[Subtitles by danielsangeo]
Wait, this isn't gonna work.
If a rescue team comes, that gun's
gonna turn them into peppered steak.
[scientist sneezes]
Good idea.
[whistling noise]
Yep.
[turret firing]
[turret beeps]
You're right.
There's a firing delay
[turret beeps]
when it's not beeping.
And there's another bug!
[turret beeps]
Damn, these things are faster
than the centipedes in my house!
[turret beeps]
Eh, screw it.
I'll just wait until the beeping stops,
[turret beeps]
then make a dash for it.
It's just as well.
[turret deactivating]
I wasn't looking forward to staying here
and cannibalizing that guy for food.
Oh, back for more, huh?
SCIENTIST: Don't you think we
should...wait here for a while?
Nah, you're on your own, chump.
[whistling sound]
Pew!
[turret beeps]
Sweet!
Man, that guy back there is just screwed.
[turret beeps]
Well, once again, not my problem.
Oh, what the--
[headcrab squeals]
OKAY, CHILDREN, CLASS IS IN SESSION!
EVERYONE TAKE YOUR SEATS!
I SAID, "EVERYONE TAKE YOUR SEATS!"
DAMMIT, BILLY, THAT MEANS YOU, TOO!
TAKE YOUR SEAT!
Okay, now today's lesson is
on--wait, what am I doing?
I don't know.
Y'know, facial lacerations aside,
that was pretty pimp of me.
[gunfire]
I need a sword.
And a helmet.
And a horse.
Yeah.
Hey, can I have your gun?
I thought it'd be cool to shoot
people with two pistols
like I'm in a John Woo movie or something.
Uhh...
Fine, don't say anything, ya freak.
Oh, I guess he was using it.
Still, one gun is fun,
but two is Woo-tastic.
[ceiling tiles fall]
What?
[headcrab squeals]
Gah!  Dammit!
I'm getting sick of these face-huggers
trying to French me.
It's not like I'm that hard up.
Christ.
Oh, what's this?
Oh, doing the vent thing, huh?
Yeah, I was--
[alien growls, scientists scream]
Ugh!  You dumbasses!
You can't go through the fan blades!
Some people just have to
learn things the hard way.
I mean, it only took me one time to
learn not to stick your head in a fan.
[vortigaunt charging up]
Oh no...
[vortigaunt bolt]
DAAAH!
Quit zapping me!
Let's see how you like it!
Dammit!
Have to reload...
Okay, pumpkinhead.
[vortigese]
Gah!  These aliens suck!
I'm already afraid of Muppets;
I don't need this on top of that!
Come out!
[whistles]
They're not coming.
You guys are even worse than the
face-huggers, you know that?
I need a name for you.
I'm just going to call you 'zappers'
until I can think of something better.
Where the hell are they?
[vortigese]
Oh, I can hear them.
I'd better check my flank.
That's how they got
that dude in Jurassic Park.
Oh, wait, those were raptors.
Well, I'd shoot them, too.
[vortigaunt charging up]
Bastard!
[vortigaunt bolt]
[shudders]
THAT'S SO FRIGGIN' ANNOYING!
It's not like the electricity
kills me; it just hurts!
I'm not sure what I'm more upset about:
that they're shocking me,
or that I can't shoot
electricity from my hands.
I'm going backwards again, aren't I?
[vortigese]
Boom!
Oh, I see you, too!
Oh, man!  I shoot one
long-distance through a window
and another one that's
waiting to jump me!
That is James Bond intuition!
Damn, I'm awesome!
[hums James Bond theme]
[ceiling tiles fall]
Dooh-duh-DAH-DAH! Duh, dehduh!
How did that thing know I was here?
How many of you fuckers are
there?
Do you want me to individually engrave
your names on each of my bullets?
Is my gun not personal enough for you?
I'll kill every last one of you bastards.
All I need are bullets.
We have a lot of bullets here!
EARTH IS A MINERAL-RICH PLANET!
I BET YOURS SUCKS!
It's probably a swamp
planet with no metal!
And, if it's not, you probably
belong in a swamp, anyway!
You should be out killing
vacationing college students,
not scientists trying to get
work do--
[gagging]
[barnacle chirping]
What the fuck?!
Now, I'm covered in blood!
In my hair...
This is going to jam my gun.
And, what about you?
Enjoying the show?
SCIENTIST: I just overheard the
secure access transmission.
SCIENTIST: Soldiers have arrived
and they're coming to rescue us.
SCIENTIST: Of course, I have my doubts
that we'll live long enough to greet them.
YEAH, THANKS FOR THE WARNING, ASSHOLE!
I REALLY APPRECIATE HOW YOU
STOOD THERE STARING AT ME
AND NOT DOING A GOD DAMNED THING!
YOU'RE LIKE A CAT WATCHING A MOUSE DIE!
I'm getting out of here.
There's too many psychos in this place.
[whistling sound]
What's that noise?
[turret firing]
WAAAH!
MY EAR!
[turret beeping]
I GOT SHOT IN THE EAR!
WHY IS THE BUILDING TRYING TO
KILL ME?!
[turret beeping]
I'M AN EMPLOYEE!
YOU DON'T SHOOT YOUR EMPLOYEES!
[turret beeping]
You are NOT employees!
DAMMIT!
[turret beeping]
YOU'RE ALL FIRED!
[turret firing]
NO!
[turret beeping]
Fuck this.
I'm going to wait for that thing
to power down.
[turret beeping, whistling in time]
[turret beeping]
I can't believe that we have
automatic turret guns.
[turret beeping]
You shouldn't kill your workers.
[turret deactivating]
I thought they taught that in,
like, Business 101.
Okay...
[imitating Bionic Man sound]
Man, I just don't get a break.
Kneel before me!  Ha ha ha ha ha ha....
Hah, no smoking around the turret gun.
Bad for your health.
[vortigese]
Oh, oh!
Yeah, keep on gargling; I'm reloading.
And that's why you should stay in school.
Man, I am not happy at all about
getting my ear shot.
I guess it's a free piercing,
but I don't have a mirror.
I don't want to look like I'm gay.
I guess gay is when you
get both ears pierced.
Either that, or you're a sailor.
GUARD: Are you thinking what I'm thinking?
Who the hell are you talking to?
Friggin' lunatic.
GUARD: Hey, what the hell are you doing
down here?  Get topside!
GUARD: I hear troops are
coming in to save us.
Well, they're not coming fast enough!
I got shot, y'know?
Ah, first aid.  Yeah.
I need some gauze.
GUARD: I'll bet that stings a bit.
Yeah, no shit, Skippy.  I've got more
blood on me than an ax murderer.
I'd be arrested if I were to
approach a child looking like this.
I wonder if there's
any more clips in here.
I'm on my last one.
I really wasn't expecting to use up
all my ammo, but what can I say?
This gun keeps solving my
problems for me.
Oh!  An exit sign!
It's about bloody time.
[lock jiggles]
Okay, remain calm.
Jesus!
Okay, we'll take this to the next level.
What the fuck?!
We installed bullet-proof
glass on our exit doors?
That stuff's not cheap.
How retarded are we?
[lock jiggles]
I don't know anymore.
Ugh.  What did they think
was going to happen?
The turret guns were going to sprout
a pair of legs and get up and leave?
I'm just a rat in a maze.
With no cheese.
And you're not helping.
I guess I am getting a
gun out of the whole deal.
That's registered in someone else's name!
That means, once all this blows over,
I'll be able to kill anyone and
get away with it if I want to.
Hey, I think that's an exit.
[ceiling tiles fall]
Huh?
[headcrabs chirp]
Oh my God!
THIS WAS NOT APPROVED BY THE COMMITTEE!
I'M NOT TAKING ANY QUESTIONS!
NO COMMENT!
Well, I can understand how some
people can't get enough of me,
but it's for their own good, really.
Yay, something I can actually break.
God, my face must look like a
cutting board right now.
I wonder if it'll scar.
That would look badass if I had one
of those face scars across the eye.
And my ear.
Who else has pierced ears?
Artists,
punk rockers,
pirates...
Huh, pirates have both ears pierced.
But, then, they're sailors.
Hey, is that coffee?
Sweet, are there any doughnuts?
Whoa!  That's a big no.
This isn't going to work.
What the... they're deaf.
They can't hear me.
How the hell did they find me earlier?
They don't have eyes.
We may never know.
Science will thank me someday.
Alright, enough of this, I'm
getting some coffee.
Now, which button?
Yeah, that's the stuff.